'Cause at the end
I assumed there'd be nurses.
(Sheldon:)Well, this is highly insulting.
(Amy:)Sheldon, don't overreact.
(Sheldon:)I'm the child
she was worried about?
(Sheldon:)I have a brother and sister
(Sheldon:)whose combined
intellectual wattage
(Sheldon:)couldn't power a potato clock,
(Sheldon:)if I spotted them the potato.
(Amy:)Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
(Amy:)Blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah.
(Sheldon:)What?
(Sheldon:)Well, I was in my room,
(Sheldon:)I couldn't hear
what they were saying.
(Amy:)I'll take over from here.
(Amy:)He's been in there a long time.
(Amy:)Should I go talk to him?
(Mary:)He's upset with me. I should be
the one who talks to him.
(Amy:)Are you going to?
(Mary:)Oh, heck no.